I woke up early with my serious smile Turned on the tube and stared for a while No LeVar Burton, no reading Rainbow No more surprises on the Antiques Roadshow Where did Bob Ross go with his happy trees?
No more educational shows teaching me about bees And the guy from Zoom who used to shout, Hey yo!
Is that looking for a job at Trader Joe's?
This program was brought to you by the letters F and U And viewers like me, well we got screwed too They told us lies, we took the bait They just wanted a bigger piece of cake They stole Mr. Rogers, just to keep their tax break Big Bird slipping fries, Kermit's in disguise Oscar's got a podcast just ranting at the sky PBS is gone, NPR's in debt They may have been defunded but they're not gone yet
Where in the world is Carmen Sandiego?
Somewhere on hold with Wells Fargo.
Arthur got cancelled for pushing respect.
And now there's a show called Tax Credits for Pets.
They fired Kyle Kassel, stole his voice for an ad.
Now he reads disclaimers for CryptoDad.
A clip of the Big Red Dogs now parade.
Because kids don't read, they school all day.
Money bank shut it.
To education, how?
Money was free.
True inspiration, why?
Help Chancellor!
That's not profitable.
Why?
So what do we get?
Nothing!
Stop being intolerable.
This message was brought to you by the Redder's WTF.
Our Alphabet's shrinking, we're down to just amps.
P is for panic, B is for broke, S is for Sesame.
Just kidding, that's toast.
Elmo's doing TikToks for old men in suits.
Julia's been replaced by A.I.
which ruins.
Maria's gone.
Louie's gone bald.
Hank Grover's just selling supplements.
He's tapping Rick Percott.
Good night, moon.
Good night, hope.
Good night, Bill Nye and the Antiques Roadshow.
Good night, Big Bird.
Good night, Frontline.
I'll see you all again in privatized time.
Today's show was made possible by... Absolutely no one!